questions = [
    {
        "question": "In which continent are Chile, Argentina and Brazil?",
        "options": ["North America", "South America", "Europe", "Asia"],
        "answer": "South America"
    },
    {
        "question": """Which brand of soup featured
                       in one of Andy Warhols most famous
                       pop art pieces?""",
        "options": ["Heinz", "Campbells", "Baxters", "Knorr"],
        "answer": "Campbells"
    },
    {
        "question": """The Mad Hatter and the Cheshire Cat
                       are characters in which famous book?""",
        "options": ["Winne-the-Pooh", "Charlottes Web",
                    "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory",
                    "Alice in Wonderland"],
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What measurement scale is used to determine wind speed?",
        "options": ["Beaufort scale", "Richter scale",
                    "Synoptic scale", "Gusting scale"],
        "answer": "Beaufort scale"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sides does a dodecahedron have?",
        "options": ["2", "24", "14", "20"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": """The Statue of Liberty was a gift to the United States
                       from which European country?""",
        "options": ["Belgium", "Germany", "Spain", "France"],
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the worlds fastest species of bird?",
        "options": ["Golden eagle", "Peregrine falcon",
                    "Frigatebird", "Penguin"],
        "answer": "Peregrine falcon"
    },
    {
        "question": """Which animated Disney movie features characters
                       including Rafiki and Zazu?""",
        "options": ["The Jungle Book", "The Lion King", "Finding Nemo",
                    "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"],
        "answer": "The Lion King"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which female holds the most Wimbledon titles?",
        "options": ["Martina Navratilova", "Serena Williams",
                    "Venus Williams", "Martina Hingis"],
        "answer": "Martina Navratilova"
    },
    {
        "question": """Which Danish-Norwegian band released the hit song
                       Barbie Girl in 1997?""",
        "options": ["ABBA", "Aqua", "Vanilla Ice", "Bjork"],
        "answer": "Aqua"
    },
]
